<Publish>
	<ModId Value="81157" />
	<DisplayName Value="AreaBucket" />
	<ShortDescription Value="(BETA) A Cities XL like surface filling tool" />
	<LongDescription>
(BETA) A mod provides tool like Cities XL decoration tool,
should works on any prefab that can be created by vanilla surface/area tool(District, Lots, Surfaces, MapTiles, etcs.).

The tool now can detect road edges, surfaces, sub net, net lanes (like assets in EDT's UI panel) as boundaries
and try to filling then in one click.

Please feel free to ask any questions,
bugs or suggestions can be posted here, you can also see some demostration video for this tool: https://discord.gg/HxJn5XHY

After installing the mod, you can see extra "Area Bucket" switch button on tool options panel when picking any surface assets,
press to active it and more tool's options will be shown.

### 2024/09/21 UPDATE

New tool "Area Replacement Tool" is added into mod, you can see the activation button just next to original AreaBucket tool button.
(use vanilla road replacement icon)

New tool allows you to quickly replace any existing surfaces/spaces. But for this tool one thing to note:
* if the surfaces/spaces belongs to any buildings, replacement will break original owning relationship 
(for example, delete building will not remove surfaces been replaced)


## IMPORTANT NOTES
Two experimental options(subnet/netlane boudaries, check crossing boundaries) have minor performance issue and will slow down the fps while using the tool

### Assets that can use this tool:
* Surfaces, including custom surfaces assets
### Assets that can not use this tool currently (plan to bring this tool for those assets in the future):
* Specialized Industries Lot
* Garbage LandFill Lot
* Districts
* MapTiles

The mod now is on beta progress, known issues below:
* Performance issue for some options in large filling range (now it major comes from detect boundary crossing, secondly is the flooding option)
* "Invalid Shape" notification sometime happens, but in most cases the filling areas can still be plopped.
You can active Anarchy in tool options panel to hide the warning.
* Sometime surface placing may failed because of some extremely sharp corner being filled

### Acknowledgement
* Thanks to Krzychu and Macsergey's sharing and suggestion for game key-bindings. Thanks to Yenyang's sharing and helps in many places

  </LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/img5.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/img6.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/img7.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/flooding.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/flooding2.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/settings.jpg" />
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<ModVersion Value="0.5.3" />
	<GameVersion Value="1.3.*" />

  <Dependency Id="74417" /> <!--Dependency Unified Icon Library -->

  <!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
  <ChangeLog>

Try to fix Crash to Desktop issues on game version 1.3.3f1

Add version in Setting.

Slightly optimize performance when Boundary Crossing enabled

  </ChangeLog>
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/Cmyna/AreaBucket" />
  <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HxJn5XHY" />
</Publish>
