<Publish>
	<ModId Value="81157" />
	<DisplayName Value="AreaBucket" />
	<ShortDescription Value="(BETA) A Cities XL like surface filling tool" />
	<LongDescription>
(BETA) A mod provides tool like Cities XL decoration tool,
should works on any prefab that can be created by vanilla surface/area tool(District, Lots, Surfaces, MapTiles, etcs.).
    
The tool now can detect road edges, surfaces, sub net, net lanes (like assets in EDT's UI panel) as boundaries 
and try to filling then in one click.

Please feel free to ask any questions, 
bugs or suggestions can be posted here, you can also see some demostration video for this tool: 
https://discord.com/channels/1024242828114673724/1237985243420561479

After installing the mod, you can see extra "Area Bucket" switch button on tool options panel when picking any surface assets,
press to active it and more tool's options will be shown.

## IMPORTANT NOTES
Two experimental options(sun net boudaries, check crossing boundaries) have serious performance issues.
They will slow down the FPS on large filling range. Be careful to use them

### Assets that can use this tool:
* Surfaces, including custom surfaces assets
### Assets that can not use this tool currently (plan to bring this tool for those assets in the future):
* Specialized Industries Lot
* Garbage LandFill Lot
* Districts
* MapTiles

The mod now is on beta progress, known issues below:
* Minor Performance issue for some options in large filling range (sub net boundaries, detect boundaries crossing)
* "Invalid Shape" notification happens offen, but the filling areas can still be plopped. 
You can active Anarchy in tool options panel to hide the warning
* still generate some gaps when filling, especially on the boundaries crossing
(enable experimental options and active boundaries crossing in tool option can alleviate the problem)
  </LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/img1.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/img2.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/img3.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/img4.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/img5.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/img6.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Images/img7.jpg" />
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<ModVersion Value="0.2.0" />
	<GameVersion Value="1.*" />

  <Dependency Id="74417" /> <!--Dependency Unified Icon Library -->

  <!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
  <ChangeLog>
features: 
* new filling boundary option - net lanes. It will be usefull filling polygons drawed by net lanes 
(like net lanes provided by EDT's panel )
* Anarchy support - the tool option panel will show anarchy's mod options. So you can hide overlapping/invalid shape warning when using the tool

Performance improvement: new optimization for filling tools. It will be much smoother than before if setting filling range over 100m with experimental options
  </ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/Cmyna/AreaBucket" />
  <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.com/channels/1024242828114673724/1237985243420561479" />
</Publish>
